KENNETH PROBECK

10 Wentworth Drive, Dix Hills, NY 11746 | (516)-713-2208 | kxp4109@g.rit.edu

Objective

To obtain a cooperative education, or paid intership, position as a game programmer or a software development programmer, available Summer 2017.

Portfolio: kprobeck.github.io

Projects

- Designed and balanced a table-top game, "inDICEsion," a game where foam dice are thrown at boards to score points, or can be thrown to knock other players' dice out of the competition. This is a family-friendly game built for anywhere from 2 to 6 players. Game complete with a team size of five people over the span of a six week process.
- Programmed and designed User Interface, animations, and created levels for "ColorCoded," a
 Puzzle game built for mobile using Unity. Created artwork, animations and all User Interface
 for the application, providing a friendly user experience. Team size of five people over the
 span fo six weeks, currently expanding on the project with a team size of three. Currently in
 the Semi-Finals for the Microsoft Imagine Cup 2017.

Education

Bachelor of Science: Game Design and Development Rochester Institute of Technology - Rochester, NY Current

- GPA: 3.8 / 4.0
- · Dean's List all terms, Presidential Scholarship
- · Relevant Classes:
 - Object-Oriented Programming and Structures
 - Data Structures and Algorithms
 - · 3D and 2D Animation and Asset Production
 - · Level Design
 - Math Graphical Simulation
 - · Rich Media Development
 - · Web Design and Development

Skills

Visual StudioC# / C++Adobe PhotoshopJavascript

Adobe Illustrator
 HTML5 / CSS3

Unity
 Autodesk Maya 2016

Unreal Engine
 Microsoft Office

Work Experience

Cooker / Server

August 2015 to Current

Rochester Institute of Technology - Rochester, NY

- Prepare and serve food to customer specifications.
- · Maintain a clean work area.
- · Work in a busy environment, processing many orders quickly and correctly.

Cashier and Footwear Sales Associate

Bob's Clothing Store - East Northport, NY

- Helped customer purchase apparel from the store.
- Provided quality customer service to all customers.
- Provided additional information to customers anywhere around the store.

August 2015 to Current

December 2012 to December 2014